Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - Go (Box 107)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 107)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 107)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 107)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 107)
  - Go (Box 108)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 108)
  - Goff, Horace Porter and Parents, 1912-1918 (Box 108)
  - Gol (Box 108)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 108)
    - 1921-1931 (Box 108)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 108)
  - Golde, 1923-1937 (Box 108)
  - Golds, 1923-1937 (Box 108)
  - Goldsmiths and Sons, 1915-1936 (Box 108)
  - Gom-Gon, 1913-1923 (Box 108)
  - Gonce, Herschel W., 1924; 1929-1931 (Box 108)
  - Goo-Gop (Box 108)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 108)
    - 1917-1923 (Box 108)
  - Goo (Box 108)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 108)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 108)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 108)
  - Goodbody, Walter (Box 108)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 108)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 108)
  - Goodell, C.E., undated (Box 108)
  - Goodm, 1923-1937 (Box 108)
  - Goodrich, B.F. Co., 1913-1914 (Box 108)
  - Goodrich, James P., 1917-1920 (Box 108)
  - Gor (Box 108)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 108)
  - Gor (Box 109)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 109)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 109)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 109)
  - Gos-Got, 1913-1923 (Box 109)
  - Gos, 1923-1929 (Box 109)
  - Gos (Box 109)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 109)
  - Goshen College, 1913-1937 (Box 109)
  - Gou-Goz, 1913-1923 (Box 109)
  - Gould, M.L., 1917-1918 (Box 109)
  - Gra (Box 109)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 109)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 109)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 109)
  - Gr (Box 109)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 109)
    - 1926 (Box 109)
    - 1927 (Box 109)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 109)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 109)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 109)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 109)
  - Graduate Council, 1915-1917 (Box 109)
  - Graduate School, 1930 (Box 109)
  - Grah (Box 110)
    - 1924-1929 (Box 110)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 110)
  - Graham, 1913-1923 (Box 110)
  - Gran (Box 110)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 110)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 110)
  - Granger and Bollenbacher (Box 110)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 110)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 110)
    - January-August 1931 (Box 110)
    - September-December 1931 (Box 110)
    - January-April 1932 (Box 110)
    - May-December 1932 (Box 110)
    - 1933 (Box 110)
    - 1934 (Box 110)
    - 1935 (Box 110)
    - 1936 (Box 110)
    - 1937 (Box 110)
  - Grasselli Chemical Company, 1914-1923 (Box 110)
  - Grav, 1923-1937 (Box 110)
  - Gray, 1913-1923 (Box 110)
  - Gre (Box 110)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 110)
  - Gre (Box 111)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 111)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 111)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 111)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 111)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 111)
  - Greathouse, Charles A., 1914-1919 (Box 111)
  - Greek Department: letter of application and recommendation for a new head, 1936 (Box 111)
  - Green (Box 111)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 111)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 111)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 111)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 111)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 111)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 111)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 111)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 111)
  - Green, G. Victor, 1925-1927 (Box 111)
  - Greenough, Walter S., 1914; 1917-1920 (Box 111)
  - Greg, 1923-1937 (Box 111)
  - Gregory Electric Company, 1918-1924 (Box 111)
  - Gri (Box 111)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 111)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 111)
  - Gri (Box 112)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 112)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 112)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 112)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 112)
  - Griffin-Griffith, 1913-1923 (Box 112)
  - Griffith, Arthur, undated (Box 112)
  - Grig, 1923-1937 (Box 112)
  - Grimes, L.M.—correspondence about Mrs. Whisenand Fund, 1924 (Box 112)
  - Gris, 1923-1931 (Box 112)
  - Gro (Box 112)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 112)
  - Gro (Box 112)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 112)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 112)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 112)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 112)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 112)
  - Grose, G.R., 1913-1920 (Box 112)
  - Grot, 1923-1937 (Box 112)
  - Gru-Gry, 1913-1923 (Box 112)
  - Gru, 1923-1937 (Box 112)
  - Gua-Guk, 1913-1923 (Box 112)
  - Gul-Gun, 1913-1923 (Box 112)
  - Gu (Box 112)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 112)
  - Gu (Box 113)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 113)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 113)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 113)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 113)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 113)
  - Guo-Guz, 1913-1923 (Box 113)
  - Gur, 1923-1936 (Box 113)
  - Gw, 1915-1924 (Box 113)
  - Gwaltney, Bernita, undated (Box 113)
  - Gy, 1913-1923 (Box 113)
  - H (Box 113)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 113)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 113)
    - 1927 (Box 113)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 113)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 113)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 113)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 113)
  - Haa-Haf, 1913-1923 (Box 113)
  - Haas, Flora Anderson, 1928-1930 (Box 113)
  - Hac, 1923-1937 (Box 113)
  - Hag-Hak, 1913-1919 (Box 113)
  - Hag-Hak (Box 113)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 113)
  - Hag, 1923-1937 (Box 113)
  - Haggerty, M.E., 1913-1916 (Box 114)
  - Hah, 1923-1937 (Box 114)
  - Hal (Box 114)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 114)
    - 1917-1920 (Box 114)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 114)
    - 1923 (Box 114)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 114)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 114)
    - 1928 (Box 114)
    - 1929 (Box 114)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 114)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 114)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 114)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 114)
  - Hall, Professor Ford P., 1934-1937 (Box 114)
  - Hall, N.C., 1913-1917 (Box 114)
  - Halla, 1923-1937 (Box 114)
  - Halsey, Stuart & Company, 1919-1921 (Box 114)
  - Ham (Box 114)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 114)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 114)
  - Ham (Box 115)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 115)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 115)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 115)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 115)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 115)
  - Hammacher, Schlemmer & Company, 1913-1914 (Box 115)
  - Hamilton, R.I., 1913-1917 (Box 115)
  - Hamm (Box 115)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 115)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 115)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 115)
  - Hampton, Volney—correspondence regarding the traveling theatre, 1934-1935 (Box 115)
  - Han-Hap (Box 115)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 115)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 115)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 115)
  - Han (Box 115)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 115)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 115)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 115)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 115)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 115)
  - Hanley, E.A., 1913-1917 (Box 115)
  - Hanover College (Box 115)
    - 1913-1929 (Box 115)
  - Hanover College (Box 116)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 116)
  - Hans (Box 116)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 116)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 116)
  - Hara-Harp (Box 116)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 116)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 116)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 116)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 116)
  - Har (Box 116)
    - 1923 (Box 116)
    - 1924 (Box 116)
    - 1925 (Box 116)
    - 1926 (Box 116)
    - 1927 (Box 116)
    - 1928 (Box 116)
    - 1929 (Box 116)
    - 1930 (Box 116)
  - Har (Box 116)
    - 1931 (Box 116)
    - 1932 (Box 116)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 116)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 116)
  - Har, 1937 (Box 117)
  - Harbison, 1913-1937 (Box 117)
  - Harbison, Mary, 1918-1937 (Box 117)
  - Harding, Samuel B., 1913-1918 (Box 117)
  - Harding, President Warren G., undated (Box 117)
  - Harger, Rollo, undated (Box 117)
  - Harl (Box 117)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 117)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 117)
  - Harlan, Mabel M., 1924-1937 (Box 117)
    (Dept. of Romance Languages / Dept. of Spanish)
  - Harr (Box 117)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 117)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 117)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 117)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 117)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 117)
    - 1928 (Box 117)
    - 1929 (Box 117)
    - 1930 (Box 117)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 117)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 117)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 117)
  - Harris, A.W., 1913-1917 (Box 117)
  - Harris Bros. Co., 1913-1914; 1919-1921 (Box 117)
  - Harris, Robert F., 1914-1915 (Box 117)
  - Hars-Harz (Box 117)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 117)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 117)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 117)
  - Hart (Box 117)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 117)
  - Hart (Box 118)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 118)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 118)
  - Hartm (Box 118)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 118)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 118)
  - Hartzler, John E., 1913-1918 (Box 118)
  - Harvard University—Cambridge, Mass. (Box 118)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 118)
  - Harvard University (Box 118)
    - 1924-1930 (Box 118)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 118)
    - Tercentenary, 1936 (Box 118)
  - Has (Box 118)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 118)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 118)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 118)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 118)
  - Hastings, John S., 1935-1937 (Box 118)
  - Hat-Hau, 1913-1923 (Box 118)
  - Hat (Box 118)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 118)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 118)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 118)
  - Hatfield Electric Company, 1919-1925 (Box 118)
  - Hatfield, Frank H. (Box 118)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 118)
  - Hatfield, Frank H (Box 119)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 119)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 119)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 119)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 119)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 119)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 119)
  - Hav-Haw (Box 119)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 119)
    - 1921-1937 (Box 119)
  - Haw (Box 119)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 119)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 119)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 119)
  - Hawk, Charles L., 1914 (Box 119)
  - Haworth, Paul L., 1914-1925 (Box 119)
  - Hawthorne, Charles W., 1929-1930 (Box 119)
  - Hau-Haz, 1913-1919 (Box 119)
  - Hay-Haz, 1920-1923 (Box 119)
  - Hay (Box 119)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 119)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 119)
  - Hay (Box 119)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 119)
  - Hayes Brothers Inc., 1922-1931 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, E.C. (Box 119)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 119)
    - Physical Education, 1932 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, O.L. & Jensen, Otto K.—state examiners, 1933-1934 (Box 120)
  - Hays, Charles (Box 120)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 120)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 120)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 120)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 120)
    - 1935 (Box 120)
    - 1936 (Box 120)
    - 1937 (Box 120)
  - Haz, 1923-1930 (Box 120)
  - He (Box 120)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 120)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 120)
    - 1928 (Box 120)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 120)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 120)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 120)
    - 1935 (Box 120)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 120)
  - Heads of departments and deans (Box 120)
    - 1920-1926 (Box 120)
    - 1927-1937 (Box 120)
  - Hea-Hec (Box 120)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 120)
  - Hea-Hec (Box 121)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 121)
  - Heating Plant, 1914 (Box 294)
  - Hec, 1923-1937 (Box 121)
  - Hed-Heh, 1913-1923 (Box 121)
  - Hei-Hek, 1913-1923 (Box 121)
  - Hei (Box 121)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 121)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 121)
  - Heighway, George F.—alumni secretary (Box 121)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 121)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 121)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 121)
  - Heil, Henry—Chemical Company (Box 121)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 121)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 121)
    - 1918-1922 (Box 121)
  - Hel-Hem, 1913-1923 (Box 121)
  - Hel (Box 121)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 121)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 121)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 121)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 121)
  - Helm, Mark P., 1927-1928 (Box 121)
  - Hen-Heq (Box 121)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 121)
  - Hen-Hep (Box 121)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 121)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 121)
  - Hen (Box 121)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 121)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 121)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 121)
  - Hen-Heq (Box 122)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 122)
  - Hen (Box 122)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 122)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 122)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 122)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 122)
  - Hendricks, Cecilia Hennel, 1913-1937 (Box 122)
  - Henn, 1923-1937 (Box 122)
  - Hennel, Cora B. (Box 122)
    - 1914-1923 (Box 122)
    - 1923-1937 (Box 122)
  - Henry, Edna G. (Box 122)
    - 1913 (Box 122)
    - January - June 1914 (Box 122)
    - July - December 1914 (Box 122)
    - January - June 1915 (Box 122)
    - July - December 1915 (Box 122)
    - January - June 1916 (Box 122)
    - July - December 1916 (Box 122)
    - January - June 1917 (Box 122)
    - July - December 1917 (Box 122)
    - January - June 1918 (Box 122)
    - July - December 1918 (Box 122)
    - 1919 (Box 122)
    - 1920 (Box 122)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 122)
    - 1924-1937 (Box 122)
  - Hepburn, Charles M. (Box 123)
    - 1915-1919 (Box 123)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 123)
    - 1922 (Box 123)
    - 1922 (August 28) (Box 123)
    - 1923 (Box 123)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 123)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 123)
  - Her (Box 123)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 123)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 123)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 123)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 123)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 123)
  - Herold, Don, 1928-1933 (Box 123)
  - Herr, 1924-1937 (Box 123)
  - Herron, James Pat, 1922 (Box 123)
  - Hershey, A.S. (Box 123)
    - 1914 (Box 123)
    - 1914-1932 (Box 123)
  - Hershey, Mrs. L. Susanne, undated (Box 123)
  - Hershman, Joseph B., 1928-1932, 1937 (Box 123)
  - Hes-Het, 1913-1923 (Box 123)
  - Hes (Box 123)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 123)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 123)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 123)
  - Heu-Hez, 1913-1937 (Box 124)
  - Hia-Hik (Box 124)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 124)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 124)
  - Hi (Box 124)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 124)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 124)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 124)
    - 1929 (Box 124)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 124)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 124)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 124)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 124)
  - Hibben, William G., 1916-1917 (Box 124)
  - Hibbon, J.G., 1914-1916 (Box 124)
  - Hicks, John W.—chief accountant, 1937 (Box 124)
  - Hide, Leather & Belting Co., 1917-1919 (Box 124)
  - Hig (Box 124)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 124)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 124)
  - Hil (Box 124)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 124)
    - 1915-1919 (Box 124)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 124)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 124)
  - Hil (Box 125)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 125)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 125)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 125)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 125)
  - Hill, Professor John M., 1924-1937 (Box 125)
  - Hills, E.C. (Box 125)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 125)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 125)
    - 1922 (Box 125)
  - Him-Hip (Box 125)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 125)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 125)
  - Hin (Box 125)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 125)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 125)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 125)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 125)
  - Hindsley, Mark Hubert, 1923-1929 (Box 125)
  - Hinkle, Daisy Estelle, 1929-1937 (Box 125)
  - Hir-Hiz, 1913-1923 (Box 125)
  - Hir (Box 125)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 125)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 125)
  - History and Political Science, Department of, 1914 (Box 125)
  - Hj, 1915-1920 (Box 125)
  - Hoa-Hoe (Box 125A)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 125A)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 125A)
  - Ho (Box 125A)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 125A)
  - Ho (Box 126)
    - 1925 (Box 126)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 126)
    - 1928 (Box 126)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 126)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 126)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 126)
    - 1935 (Box 126)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 126)
  - Hod (Box 126)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 126)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 126)
  - Hoeflin, Cordelia—Director of Nurse's Training School (Box 126)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 126)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 126)
    - 1937 (Box 126)
  - Hof (Box 126)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 126)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 126)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 126)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 126)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 126)
  - Hoffman, H.A., 1913-1921 (Box 126)
  - Hog-Hok, 1913-1923 (Box 126)
  - Hog (Box 126)
    - 1924-1929 (Box 126)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 126)
  - Hogate, E.G. (Box 127)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 127)
    - 1915-1918 (Box 127)
  - Hola-Holl (Box 127)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 127)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 127)
    - 1919 (Box 127)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 127)
  - Hol (Box 127)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 127)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 127)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 127)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 127)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 127)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 127)
  - Holland, J.E.P.—university physician, 1914-1916 (Box 127)
  - Holland, J.E.P. (Box 127)
    - 1917 (Box 127)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 127)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 127)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 127)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 127)
  - Holland, J.E.P. (Box 128)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 128)
  - Hollett, John E., 1923-1929 (Box 128)
  - Holm (Box 128)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 128)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 128)
  - Holm-Holz (Box 128)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 128)
    - 1917-September 1919 (Box 128)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 128)
  - Holt, 1923-1937 (Box 128)
  - Hom-Hoo (Box 128)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 128)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 128)
  - Home and School Education Society, 1922 (Box 128)
  - Hon, 1923-1937 (Box 128)
  - Hoo (Box 128)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 128)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 128)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 128)
    - 1931 (Box 128)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 128)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 128)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 128)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1917-1918 (Box 128)
  - Hop (Box 128)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 128)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 128)
  - Hor (Box 128)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 128)
  - Hor (Box 129)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 129)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 129)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 129)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 129)
  - Hos-Hov (Box 129)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 129)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 129)
  - Hos (Box 129)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 129)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 129)
  - Hou (Box 129)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 129)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 129)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 129)
  - House Mothers Plans, 1925-1926 (Box 129)
  - How (Box 129)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 129)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 129)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 129)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 129)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 129)
  - How-Hoz (Box 129)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 129)
  - How-Hoz (Box 130)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 130)
  - Howard, Ralph, 1929-1931 (Box 130)
    (Superintendent, Indiana State Penal Farm)
  - Howe, J.C., 1913-1917 (Box 130)
  - Howe, W.D. (Box 130)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 130)
    - 1914-1915 (Box 130)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 130)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 130)
  - Hr, undated (Box 130)
  - Hs, 1913-1917 (Box 130)
  - Hsu, Showin Wetsen, 1915-1916 (Box 130)
  - Hua-Huf (Box 130)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 130)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 130)
  - Hu (Box 130)
    - 1924 (Box 130)
    - 1925 (Box 130)
    - 1926 (Box 130)
    - 1927 (Box 130)
    - 1928 (Box 130)
    - 1929 (Box 130)
    - 1930 (Box 130)
    - 1931 (Box 130)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 130)
  - Hu (Box 130)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 130)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 130)
  - Hua-Huf (Box 130)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 130)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 130)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 130)
  - Hufford, Mason E., 1913-1937 (Box 130)
  - Hue, 1923-1937 (Box 131)
  - Hug (Box 131)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 131)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 131)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 131)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 131)
  - Hughes, Rev. Alfred P., undated (Box 131)
  - Huh-Hup (Box 131)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 131)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 131)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 131)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 131)
  - Hul (Box 131)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 131)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 131)
  - Hull, Josephine—Acting Director, Training School for Nurses, Indianapolis, 1931-1933 (Box 131)
  - Humke, Homer L., 1914-1923 (Box 131)
  - Hun (Box 131)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 131)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 131)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 131)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 131)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 131)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 131)
  - Hunnewell, F.W., 5 November 1918 (Box 132)
  - Hunnewell Committee on Education, November 8, year unknown (Box 132)
  - Hur-Hus, 1913-1919 (Box 132)
  - Hurty, John N., 1920-1923 (Box 132)
  - Hus, 1923-1937 (Box 132)
  - Hutchins, C.P., 1913-1914 (Box 132)
  - Hutchins, Frank F., 1913-1932 (Box 132)
  - Hut-Huz, 1913-1923 (Box 132)
  - Hut (Box 132)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 132)
  - Hut (Box 132)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 132)
  - Hy (Box 132)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 132)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 132)
  - Hygiene, 1920-1937 (Box 132)
  - I (Box 132)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 132)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 132)
    - 1928 (Box 132)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 132)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 132)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 132)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 132)
  - Ia-Il (Box 132)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 132)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 132)
  - Idaho, University of, Moscow, 1917-1937 (Box 132)
  - Illinois, University of, Urbana-Champaign & Chicago (Box 133)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 133)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 133)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 133)
    - 1920 (Box 133)
    - 1921 (Box 133)
    - 1922 (Box 133)
    - 1923 (Box 133)
    - 1924 (Box 133)
    - 1925 (Box 133)
    - 1926 (Box 133)
    - 1927 (Box 133)
    - 1928 (Box 133)
    - 1929 (Box 133)
    - 1930 (Box 133)
    - 1931 (Box 133)
    - 1932 (Box 133)
  - Illinois, University of, Urbana-Champaign & Chicago (Box 133)
    - 1933 (Box 133)
    - 1934 (Box 133)
    - 1935 (Box 133)
    - 1936 (Box 133)
    - 1937 (Box 133)
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1922-1937 (Box 133)
  - Illinois Electric Company, 1913-1920 (Box 133)
  - Illinois Teachers College—Eastern at Charleston, Western at Macomb, Northern at Dekalb, Southern at Carbondale Divisions, 1932-1937 (Box 134)
  - I Men, 1917-1931 (Box 134)
  - Im-Ip (Box 134)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 134)
    - 1915 (Box 134)
    - 1916 (Box 134)
    - 1917 (Box 134)
    - 1918 (Box 134)
    - 1919 (Box 134)
    - 1920 (Box 134)
    - January-June 1921 (Box 134)
    - July-December 1921 (Box 134)
    - January-June 1922 (Box 134)
    - July-December 1922 (Box 134)
    - 1923 (Box 134)
  - In (Box 134)
    - September-December 1923 (Box 134)
    - January-May 1924 (Box 134)
    - June-December 1924 (Box 134)
    - January-June 1925 (Box 134)
    - July-December 1925 (Box 135)
    - January-May 1926 (Box 135)
    - June-December 1926 (Box 135)
    - January-May 1927 (Box 135)
  - In (Box 135)
    - June-September 1927 (Box 135)
    - October-December 1927 (Box 135)
    - January-June 1928 (Box 135)
    - July-September 1928 (Box 135)
    - October-December 1928 (Box 135)
    - January-July 1929 (Box 135)
    - August-September (partial) 1929 (Box 135)
    - September (cont'd)-December 1929 (Box 135)
    - January-June 1930 (Box 135)
    - July-December 1930 (Box 135)
    - January-May 1931 (Box 135)
    - June-December 1931 (Box 135)
  - In (Box 136)
    - January-June 1932 (Box 136)
    - July-December 1932 (Box 136)
    - January-June 1933 (Box 136)
    - July-December 1933 (Box 136)
    - January-April 1934 (Box 136)
    - May-September 1934 (Box 136)
    - October-December 1934 (Box 136)
    - January-May 1935 (Box 136)
    - June-September 1935 (Box 136)
    - October-December 1935 (Box 136)
    - January-April 1936 (Box 136)
    - May-September 1936 (Box 136)
    - October-December 1936 (Box 136)
  - In (Box 136)
    - January-April 1937 (Box 136)
    - May-September 1937 (Box 136)
  - Indiana, 1923-1924 (Box 136)
  - Indiana Associated Telephone Company, 1933-1937 (Box 136)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1923-1937 (Box 136)
  - Indiana Boys' School, undated (Box 136)
  - Indiana Centennial Celebration, 1916 (Box 136)
  - Indiana, Centennial History of, 1914-1916 (Box 136)
  - Indiana Central College (Box 136)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 136)
  - Indiana Central College (Box 137)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Council of Religious Education (Box 137)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 137)
    - 1926-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Daily Student—Auditor's Report, 1915-1916 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Daily Student, 1936-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Dental College, 1923-1926 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Education Survey Commission, 1923 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Federation of Art Clubs (Box 137)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 137)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs (Box 137)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 137)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 137)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Historical Commission, 1915-1916 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Historical Society, 1923-1924 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Inspection Bureau, 1928-1932; 1936-1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Legislative Bureau, 1928; 1932; 1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Lincoln Union, 1927-1932 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Piano Company—quotation on Baldwin pianos, 1937 (Box 137)
  - Indiana School of Religion (Box 137)
    - undated (Box 137)
    - 1927-1935 (Box 137)
  - Indiana Society of Chicago, undated (Box 137)
  - Indiana Society for Mental Hygiene, 1916-1935 (Box 137)
  - Indiana State Farm, 1928-1930 (Box 137)
  - Indiana State Normal School—Terre Haute (Box 137)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 137)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 137)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 137)
    - 1926 (Box 137)
    - 1927 (Box 137)
  - Indiana State Normal School (Box 138)
    - Terre Haute (Box 138)
      - 1928 (Box 138)
      - 1929 (Box 138)
      - 1930 (Box 138)
      - 1931 (Box 138)
      - 1932 (Box 138)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 138)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 138)
      - 1937 (Box 138)
    - Eastern Division (Muncie) (Box 138)
      - 1919-1923 (Box 138)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 138)
      - 1926 (Box 138)
      - 1927 (Box 138)
      - January-June 1928 (Box 138)
      - July-December 1928 (Box 138)
      - January-June 1929 (Box 138)
      - July-December 1929 (Box 138)
      - 1930 (Box 138)
    - Eastern Division (Muncie) (Box 139)